菲比 帮我挑订婚戒指给摩妮卡好吗？
Can you help me pick an engagement ring for Monica?
我觉得好难挑喔
I can't figure this out. It's so hard.
我要选第凡内切割法还是... 公主方切割法还是...
Should I get her a Tiffany cut, or a princess cut or a...
被纸切割法
Ow! Paper cut!
你有告诉其他人吗？
Have you told anyone else?
没有 因为我不想让摩妮卡发现
No, I don't want to tell anybody. I don't want Monica to find out.
可是你告诉我了
You told me.
因为我信任你 你是我的死党之一
Well, that's because I trust you, and we're best friends...
而且你在我看目录时闯进来
and you walked in on me while I was looking at ring brochures.
进房不敲门再次大有斩获
Well, once again, not knocking pays off.
- 如果你不是在蹲马桶就好了   - 我有同感
- I only wish you hadn't been on the toilet.     - Me too.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 钱德 要不要去喝咖啡？ - 好啊 走吧
- Chandler, wanna go to the coffeehouse?     - Oh, all right.
太好了 我们正想找你们下去
Oh, perfect. We were just gonna see if you wanted to go.
不要 我们要去别家
Oh, well, we don't, because we got the other place.
真没礼貌
How rude.
抱歉 你要吃吗？
Oh, I'm sorry. You want a bite?
老友记 第六季 第二十三集
（中央咖啡厅）
你和保罗交征得怎样？
So how are things going with Paul?
- 很好   - 嗯哼
- Good.     - Huh.
- 只不过他很内敛   - 嗯
- Although, you know, he's a private guy.     - Mm-hm.
真想让他稍微敞开心胸 分享心情
You know, I wish I could get him to open up a bit. Share some feelings.
简单 把他想成打不开的罐子就对了
That's easy. You just have to think of him as a jar of pickles that won't open.
你的意思是
So, what are you saying?
你要我抓他的头冲热水敲桌子？
I should run him under hot water and bang his head against a table?
不是 那是拷问的手法
No, that's what you do when you want to get the truth out of someone.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
- 你好吗？ - 看我的
- How are you?     - Watch this.
- 嘿 保罗   - 嘿 菲比
- Hey, Paul.     - Hi, Phoebe.
你最近好吗？
So how are things going with you?
没得抱怨
Can't complain.
- 走吧   - 嘿
- Hey!     - Hi.
- 嘿 嗨 罗斯   - 我也很高兴见到你
- Great to...     - Ross, good to see you too.
- 拜 保重   - 我很好
- Good. Bye.     - You take care.
菲比 你们刚才为什么见到我们就跑？
Hey, Pheebs, what was the deal with you and Chandler blowing us off before?
很怪吧？
Ah, that was so weird, huh?
菲比 为什么？
Phoebe, why did you do it?
不是我 是钱德
I didn't do it. It was Chandler.
他...他在生你的气
He's... He's mad at you.
- 为什么？ - 拜托 你明知故问
- What? Why?     - Oh, please. I think you know why.
我想不起来
I can't think of anything.
罗斯 你是古生物学家 再往下挖深一点
Come on, Ross. You're a paleontologist. Dig a little deeper.
等等 是不是因为两个星期前 乔伊和我没找他
Wait a minute, is it because Joey and I didn't invite him to that Knicks game...
去看《尼克》球赛？
a couple weeks ago?
你觉得他会为这种事生气吗？
Do you think that's something that he'd be mad at you for?
- 应该会   - 那就是罗
- I guess it could.     - Well, then I think that's it.
他不该隐瞒他的情绪
Well, if he's angry, he really shouldn't just cover it up.
他应该老实告诉我
I wish he'd just tell me the truth.
那你应该
Well, if that's what you want...
捉他的头 去冲热水敲桌子
then you should run him under hot water and bang his head against the table.
甜心 我在中国花园订了位 可以吗？
Honey, I made a reservation at China Garden. Is that okay?
可以啊 很棒
Yeah, that's great.
但你先跟我说说话 说说你今天好不好
But first, wait, talk to me, talk to me. Tell me about your day.
蛮好的
It was fine.
好吧
Okay.
你在想什么？你现在在想什么？
Hey, what are you thinking? What are you thinking right now?
我在想你穿这条裙子很好看
That you are looking really fine in that dress.
太好了 保罗 但是...
Yeah, that's great, Paul. But, you know...
我想知道...哇 好结实
I want to know what... Wow, those are really great.
我想知道
I just want to know...
这坚固沉默的外表下 隐藏着什么
what is behind this strong, silent exterior?
俗语说静水深流
You know, they say that still waters run deep...
我想在你的心中畅游
and I want to swim in yours.
你在讲做爱的事吗？
Are you talking about having sex?
不是 保罗
No, Paul.
我一点也不了解你
I don't know anything about you.
例如你的童年 聊聊你的童年
You know, like your childhood. Tell me about your childhood.
很普通
Normal.
好 那青春期呢？青春期总是很讨厌
Okay, well, then how about puberty? Come on. That's always a painful time.
朋友找你去过夜聊天
You know, your friends invite you to a slumber party...
趁你睡着把你的手放进热水里
and stick your hand in warm water...
害你在睡袋里撒尿
while you're sleeping so that you pee in your sleeping bag.
我没碰过那种事
No, that never happened to me.
那是你走运 没碰上那个贱人莎朗麦杰斯基
Well, you're lucky you never met that bitch, Sharon Majeski.
总之...
Anyway...
其他时期有什么悔恨吗？
The rest of your life, you know. Any regrets?
没有
No.
保罗 我要求得不多
All right, Paul. I'm not asking for a lot here.
你就讲一件事 什么事都好
Just give me something. Anything.
- 好吧   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
- 我6岁那年   - 嗯哼
- When I was 6 years old...     - Mm-hm.
我想要一辆大脚踏车
I wanted a Big Wheel.
我父母却送我一个
And instead, my parents got me this little...
小鸡造型的跳跳乐
plastic chicken that you hop around on.
衰死了 小朋友都笑我
It was embarrassing. Kids made fun of me.
那一年蛮痛苦的
That was a pretty tough year.
- 太好了 你看吧   - 嗯哼
- That's great. See?     - Heh.
我觉得我比较了解你了 谢谢
I already feel like I know you a little better. Thank you.
好 我们去吃饭吧
Okay, come on. Now we can go eat. Let's go.
我好惨
It was horrible.
大家都叫我鸡弟弟
They called me "Chicken Boy."
五年级我跟别人打架 其实也不算打架
In fifth grade, I got in a fight. Well, it wasn't really a fight.
理查达伦咬我的鼻子
Richard Danville bit me on the nose.
我摔倒 这里留了个小疤
I fell down, still have a little scar right here. You can see it.
有 我看见了
Yeah, yeah. I see the scar.
保罗 你听我说 你这样分享你的心情
Listen, Paul, I think this is really great that, you know, you've shared your feelings.
真的很棒
It's really... It's beautiful.
我们现在去吃饭好吧
But, um, what do you say we go share some food?
我现在吃不下
No, I couldn't eat now.
你在说什么？你最爱吃宫保鸡丁了
What are you talking about? You love their Kung Pao chicken.
鸡？
Chicken?
- 鸡弟弟 天哪   - 对不起 我不是故意的
- Chicken Boy!     - I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that.
一无所获 逛了几百家店
Well, this is the nine millionth ring store we've been to...
还是找不到完美的戒指
and I can't find the perfect ring.
丑 丑 丑
Ugly ring, ugly ring, ugly ring...
种类真多
It's a beautiful selection.
不然你不要送戒指
Okay, so maybe you don't get her a ring.
送点不一样的
Maybe you do something different, you know?
例如订婚手镯 或是订婚皇冠
Maybe you get her an engagement bracelet. Or an engagement tiara.
订婚独立战争毛瑟枪
Ooh! An engagement Revolutionary War musket.
真高兴我是选你来帮忙
You know, I'm so glad I picked you to help me with this.
- 嗯？ - 嗯哼
- Huh?     - Uh-huh.
你能不能想像你单膝跪下
Can't you imagine getting down on one knee...
把这件漂亮的火器交给她？
and handing her this gorgeous piece of weaponry?
我还是送戒指好了
Yeah, I'm gonna stick with the ring.
这只好漂亮 我喜欢这只
Oh, this one's nice. I like it this one.
先生？大哥？我可以看这枚戒指吗？
Sir? Kind sir, can I see this one?
你找我来就是因为我会讲价
Wait a minute. This is the reason you brought me, okay?
所以接下来交给我处理
I know how to haggle. So let me handle this from here on out.
有什么需要吗？
Can I help you?
- 有 我想看那枚戒指   - 或是不看 随便
- Yes, I would like to see that ring, please.     - Or not. Whatever.
这是一只20年代的戒指
This ring is from the 1920s.
1点5克拉 两侧镶有蓝宝石
It's a one-and-a-half karat diamond with sapphires on either side.
先生 你能不能...
Sir, could I ask you to, um?
拿着戒指向我求婚？
Could you hold out that ring and ask me to marry you?
- 好   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
你愿意嫁给我吗？
Will you marry me?
天哪 就是它了
Oh, my God, that's it. That's the ring.
- 多少钱？ - 钱德 让我来
- How much is it?     - Chandler, I will handle this.
多少钱？
How much is it?
8千6百元
Eight thousand six hundred.
我们出10块钱
We will give you $10.
- 你到底想不想买？ - 想 想
- Are you interested in this ring?     - Yes. Yes.
但我只能出8千
But I can only pay $8000.
- 好 8千可以   - 我们坚持10块钱
- Okay. I can let it go for 8.     - We stand firm at $10.
- 您要怎么付帐？ - 刷卡
- How would you like to pay?     - Uh, credit card.
喔 糟了 我的卡在乔伊那边
Oh, no. No, no, but I lent my credit card to Joey.
- 我回去拿  你守住戒指   - 好的
- Okay, I'll go get it. You guard the ring.     - Okay.
刚才很抱歉
Listen, I'm sorry about before.
你们有10块钱的东西吗？
Do you have anything here for $10?
有 我有两张崭新的
Uh, yes. I have these two rather beautiful...
5元钞票
five-dollar bills.
我出1块钱跟你买
I'll give you $1 for them.
记得昨天钱德和菲比 是不是看到我们就跑？
Hey, remember how Chandler and Phoebe blew us off yesterday?
有吗？
No.
- 你当时在吃披萨   - 喔 对
- Remember, you were eating pizza?     - Yeah.
好 钱德显然是在气
Well, apparently Chandler's angry at us...
我们两星期前 没帮他买《尼克》球票
for not getting him a ticket to that Knicks game a couple weeks ago.
我们为什么要帮他买票？
What, we were supposed to just get him a ticket?
- 那家伙老是揩我们的油   - 就是啊
- That guy is always mooching off of us.     - Yeah.
但我还是觉得应该设法和解
Anyway, I still think we should try to patch things up, you know?
我们可以找他去看另一场球赛
Like, maybe we could get him tickets to another Knicks game and invite him.
好主意 而且他的卡还在我这里
Wow, that's a great idea. And I still have his credit card.
帐单
Here you go.
我有卡 拿去吧
Hey, hey. I got this one. Here you go.
有时候我真搞不懂钱德
You know, I gotta tell you, sometimes I just don't get Chandler.
我和他做很多事都没找你
You know, me and him do stuff all the time without you...
你也不会生气
and you don't get all upset.
- 很多事？ - 可多了
- All the time?     - All the time.
我的天哪 我的天哪...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- 还在哭？ - 跟小女生一样
- Still crying?     - Like a little girl.
我知道...都是我不好
I know, I know, I know. This is all my fault.
是我要他敞开心胸的
I wanted him to open up.
但是我不知道我会放出一头
But God, I didn't know that I was gonna unleash...
哭哭啼啼又黏人的怪物
this weepy, clingy, moist monster.
有两个办法能让一个男人闭嘴
You know, I only know of two sure-fire ways to shut a man up.
其中一个是性爱
And one of them is sex.
- 另一个是什么？ - 不知道
- What's the other?     - I Don't know.
我只用过第一个
I never had to use the other one.
我只是说做爱的时候 他就不能讲话
I'm just saying, you know, if we're having sex, he's not talking.
没错 话多的是你
Ah, that's right. You're the talker.
- 总之这个主意很棒   - 对
- Anyway, uh, great idea.     - Yeah.
我要去商店 我答应去帮他买面纸
Um, I gotta go to the store. I told him that I would buy him some more tissues.
- 我们这里有...   - 你们没有
- Uh, we have some here.     - No, you don't.
好 我还想试戴皇冠
Okay. Um, I'd also like to try on the tiara.
太好了
Oh, yeah. Okay.
怎么样？太花了？
Wow, what do you think? Too much?
有点 好吧
A tad.
把皇冠放回去
Then take the tiara back...
毛瑟枪再给我一次
and let me hold the musket again.
少了点什么...
Something's missing.
好 把我朋友桃的戒指拿给我
Let me see the ring that my friend picked out.
那枚20年代的钻戒呢？
Where's the 1920s princess-cut ring?
刚刚卖给那位先生了
I just sold it to that gentleman.
完蛋了
Oh, my God!
等等 别走
Wait, no!
放我出去 快点
Let me out! Now!
瑞秋...
Rachel?
不是
No.
- 保罗 你好吗？ -还好
- How are you, Paul?     - Okay.
钱德...
Chandler...
- 你爸抱过你吗？ - 没有 他抱过你吗？
- did your dad ever hug you?     - No. Did he hug you?
不是
No. No.
只不过我爸都没抱过我
It's just that my dad never did.
我好想念我爸
I miss my dad.
你可以去赌城 看我爸亲别人的爸爸
Well, you can see my dad in Vegas kissing other dads.
- 嘿 钱德？ - 怎样？
- Hey, Chandler?     - Yeah?
你能不能...
Would you?
你能不能抱我？
Would you hug me?
- 我有点忙 保罗   - 我爸以前都这么说
- I'm a little busy here, Paul.     - That's exactly what my dad used to say.
好啦 一下下 快点
Okay. A quick one. Come on, hug it out.
嗨 嗨
Hey. Hey.
行了吧
There you go.
好了
Okay.
- 再5秒钟   - 够了
- Five more seconds...     - Okay.
- 乔伊   - 什么？嗨...
- Joey!     - What? Hey, what...?
嗨 保罗是吧？
Hi. Paul, is it?
- 我的信用卡在吗？ - 在 在我的...
- Do you have my credit card?     - Yeah. It's in my...
我的口袋里
In my pocket.
- 后面的口袋   - 幸好
- My back pocket. Back pocket.     - Thank God.
- 听着 我买了今天晚上《尼克队》的票   - 我不能去
- Listen, I got tickets to the Knicks tonight.     - I can't go.
去啦 会很好玩的
Come on, it'll be fun.
我 你 罗斯和... 保罗吗？
Me, you, Ross and... Paul, probably.
钱德 我找到最完美的戒指了
Chandler, I found the perfect ring.
真不错 但我还是买之前那款好了
Oh, that's pretty nice, but I'm gonna go with the one I picked first.
天哪 钱德 那枚戒指不在了 没了
Oh, wake up, Chandler. The one you picked is gone. It's over.
什么？
What?
被一个人买走了 对不起 我想拦住他 却被关进监狱里
Some guy bought it. I'm sorry. I tried to stop him but they put me in jail.
- 把你关进监狱里？ - 门和门中间的小监狱
- They put you in jail?     - The little jail between the doors!
- 菲比 我要你守着那枚戒指   - 我知道 对不起
- Phoebe, I asked you to guard the ring.     - I know. I'm sorry.
但是这枚比较好 摩妮卡根本没看过另一枚
But, you know, this ring is better. And Monica never even saw the other ring.
但是他用那枚戒指向我求婚时 我起了鸡皮疙瘩
Yeah. But when he proposed to me with the ring, I got goose bumps.
- 也许是因为那个人   - 是因为那枚戒指
- Maybe it was the guy.     - It was the ring.
- 他兴奋吗？ - 不 他回绝了
- Hey, so was he excited about the tickets?     - No. He blew us off.
- 什么？ - 就是啊
- What?     - I know.
真是太扯了
I can't believe it.
告诉你
Can I tell you something?
我现在有点气他
I'm a little mad at him now.
告诉你
Can I tell you something?
我也是
Me too.
他生气不告诉我们
You know what? He didn't want to talk to us about being angry?
那我们也什么都不要告诉他
Well, maybe we don't talk to him at all.
噢
Ooh.
- 把他打入冷宫   - 没错
- Freeze him out.     - That's right.
- 我喜欢   - 给他好看
- I like it.     - Ah? We'll show him.
从此以后就是乔伊与罗斯 最佳拍档
From now on, it's gonna be Joey and Ross, best friends.
我们将是新的乔伊与钱德
Okay, we're gonna be the new Joey and Chandler. Ha, ha.
嗨 我回来了
Hi, I'm back.
我把我想说的话都写下来了
There's more to tell you. I've written it all down.
真好
Oh, that's great.
真是太好了
No, actually, that's...
真的好棒
That's great. That's really great.
说真的 写东西会燃起...
You know, I gotta tell you, writing, all that writing, it gets me, uh...
我的欲火
It gets me kind of hot.
等等 你听喔
Wait, wait. Listen to this:
你知道我小时候想当什么？
Know what I wanted to be when I was that age?
情圣？
A lover?
- 冲浪者   - 是吗？
- A surfer.     - Oh, yeah. A surfer?
- 我想与海浪为伍   - 等等
- I wanted to be one with the waves...     - Honey, hold on real quick.
等一下 让我把自己...弄得舒服一点
Hold on a second. Let me just get a little more comfortable here.
等一下
Wait a second.
- 这样会不会太露了？ - 不会
- This isn't too revealing, is it?     - No.
当年那个小家伙呢？
Whatever happened to that little dude?
充满梦想...
So full of dreams.
我不在乎那个小家伙
I don't care about the little dude.
我听不下去了
I can't. I cannot listen to any more of this.
只有心理医师会想听这些话
The only one who'd listen to this is a mental health professional.
那还是因为他们1小时赚1百元
And that's only because they get paid $100 an hour.
你知道我听到现在可以赚多少
Do you know how much money I could've made listening to you?
2千块钱
Two thousand dollars.
你知道我什么时候算出来的？在你碎碎念的时候
And you know when I figured that out? While you were talking.
我不敢相信 你居然想扼杀我的情绪
I can't believe you're trying to stifle me, when just 14 hours ago...
14个小时前我们才发现 那就是我妈的目的
we figured out that that's exactly what my mother was trying to do to me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不是想扼杀你的情绪
I don't mean... I didn't mean to stifle you.
我只是有点受不了
This is all just a little overwhelming.
瑞秋
Oh, Rachel.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to overwhelm you.
只不过情绪一发泄
It's just that when those gates open...
就会...不可收拾
it's hard to close them.
不过现在没事了 真的
But they are closed now. Believe me.
我很高兴你跟我分享你的心情
I'm so glad. I'm so glad you shared.
也很高兴你分享完了
And I'm glad that you're done.
那我们要不要...
So, what do you say we, um...
- 我求之不得   - 嗯哼
- I'd really like that.     - Mm-hm.
真是...太棒了
That was so good.
噢 嗯哼
Oh, oh, ugh.
- 嘿   - 我居然听你的话
- Hey.     - I can't believe you talked me into...
买下这枚造型廉价的戒指
buying this stupid gumball-machine-looking ring.
它才没有造型廉价 它很漂亮
It's not a stupid gumball-machine-looking ring. It's a beautiful ring.
它才不漂亮
No, it's not.
另一枚戒指
When I looked at the other ring...
会让我看到摩妮卡的表情
I could see Monica's face when I gave it to her...
我会看到她点头答应
and I could see her saying yes.
这枚戒指只让我看到一枚戒指
When I look at this ring, all I see is a ring.
只有近看才会看到我的眼睛
Unless I look at it really closely, and then I can see my own eye.
这是我这辈子最重要的一件事
Look, this is the most important thing I'm gonna do in my life.
我想做到最完美
I want to make sure it's perfect.
好 我们或许能把那枚戒指要回来
Okay. There may be a way that we could get the other ring back.
我偷听到那个人 准备求婚的地方
Because I heard the guy tell the jeweler where he was gonna propose.
或许我们可以说服他交换
So maybe we could get him to trade rings or something.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
你总不能给她那枚廉价的戒指吧
Well, you certainly can't give her that stupid gumball ring.
他在那里
There he is.
好 他还没求婚 因为她没有戴戒指
Okay, and he hasn't proposed yet. She has no ring on her finger.
你真行 在这之后我们应该去当侦探
Wow, you're good. After this, we should solve crimes.
没错 去请他过来
Yeah. Okay. Go get him.
好
Oh, okay.
抱歉 请您来一下 有您的电话
Excuse me, sir. Could you come with me, please? You have a phone call.
- 是谁？ - 是你的公司打来的
- Who is it?     - It is your office.
- 你知道是谁吗？ - 约翰
- Do you know who at my office?     - John.
约翰啊 太好了
Oh, John. Great.
- 他来了   - 你好
- There he is.     - Hi. Hi. Okay.
珠宝店搞错了
Okay, there was a mix-up at the jewelry store.
他们把为我保留的戒指卖给你
The ring you're about to propose with was supposed to be held for me.
所以我得跟你要回来
So I'm gonna need to have that back.
不过我愿意拿这枚美丽的 更昂贵的戒指和你交换
But in exchange, I'm willing to trade you this beautiful, more expensive ring.
哇 要是我就换
Wow, I would trade.
的确很美 但是我要用这一枚 失陪了
It is beautiful, but I'm gonna use this one. Now, if you'll excuse me.
不 这位是我的未婚妻 她就是要这枚戒指
No, no. See, this is my fiancee, and her heart was set on that ring.
你不会想伤她的心吧？
You don't want to break her heart now, do you?
对啊 你想伤一位垂死女人的心吗？
Yeah. Do you want to break a dying woman's heart?
你要死了？
You're dying?
她快死于...
Yeah, she's dying...
咳嗽了
of a cough, apparently.
对 我临死前想拥有那枚戒指 要是不能戴着它入土
It's my dying wish to have that ring. See, if I'm not buried with that ring...
我会变成孤魂野鬼在阴间...
then my spirit will wander the netherworld...
够了 亲爱的
Okay, that's enough, honey.
我不晓得
Oh, I don't know.
- 再让我看一次   - 当然 请看
- Let me see the ring.     - Great. Okay, here.
- 好吧   - 谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
- All right, I'll do it.     - Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
你即将嫁给一个大好人
And you are about to marry a wonderful man.
嘿 我要娶一个死女人
Hey, I'm marrying a dead woman.
兄弟们？
Guys?
我有大事要宣布
I got something important to tell you.
兄弟们
Guys.
兄弟们？
Guys?
我要跟摩妮卡求婚了
I'm gonna ask Monica to marry me.
我们应该让他从冷宫出来了
I think we gotta end the freeze-out.
等等 你是来真的？
Wait a minute. Is this for real?
对 戒指在这里
Yeah. Check out the ring.
天哪
Oh, my God.
你们真的是认真的？
So you two are really serious?
差不多
Yeah, pretty much.
你们要结婚了？
You're gonna get married? I mean...
我们要成为连襟了 过来
We're gonna be brothers-in-law. Come here!
- 我们又可以当朋友了   - 嗨
- And we're gonna be friends again.     - Hey.
什么？
What?
- 过去的事就别提了   - 好吧
- Water under the bridge. Forget it!     - Okay.
我本来想等搞定再说 但我还是忍不住要告诉你们
I was gonna wait till it was official, you know, but I had to tell you guys...
因为你们是我的死党
because you're my best friends.
- 我要哭出来了   - 别再哭了
- I think I'm gonna cry.     - Oh. No more crying.
拜托 我刚甩掉一个爱哭宝宝 小心我也甩了你
Please, I just dumped one crybaby. I'll dump you too.
我要跟摩妮卡求婚
I'm gonna ask Monica to marry me.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
钱德 你们会好幸福
Oh, Chandler. You guys are gonna be so happy.
- 我知道   - 面纸都死哪去了？
- I know.     - Where's all the tissues?
这是戒指
Check out the ring.
真好 至少有1点5克拉
Oh, nice. One-and-a-half karat, easy.
- 嘿   - 嘿 菲比
- Hey.     - Hey, Pheebs.
钱德要跟摩妮卡求婚了
Chandler's gonna ask Monica to marry him.
我知道 是我陪他去挑戒指的
I know. I helped pick out the ring.
噢
Oh.
你先告诉她？
You told her before you told us?
我在看戒指目录时被她撞见
She walked in while I was looking at ring brochures.
你们能谅解吧？
You can understand that, right?
兄弟们？
Guys?